Hi, and this was an I will show you how to use a wine chart to talk to hit hop to pilot.
We can use two ways in terminal and in our editor.
Let's first see how it works in terminal, in terminal we can do everything related to files,
folder manipulations, and inside of the editor we can use it to create some components,
the factory port, everything inside of existing file.
So let's show the copy of it in line chart, we can use command plus i keys to show it.
If you use windows you can use control instead of command and we can ask for example to create
some file for us, create a button dot j6 file and it provides a command and we can run
the command and file was created, so we can open it.
For example also we can ask example what just files we have in the current folder.
So we see the command after we run it, so we see the files and we can ask any other
commands related to file system.
So let's now move to button component and open in line chart from editor and ask to create
the button component, create a React button component with label prop.
You see do the creation but we have some prop types, prop types, it's library which
help you to have strict types for the props, like label should be string can require it,
but we don't want to use it, so we will ask a power don't use this library, so don't
use prop types, and we can add it code, and you see didn't update, we can also ask some
explanation, what do I want to explain, what means three dots, let's check if you provide
any answer for us, maybe let's provide some bigger context, you already respond, so
in your code the three dots is covered to spread operator or rest operator depending on the
context, here how it works in your example, it's an object distracting, label is extracted
from the props object and three dots with props collect all the remaining props into
a new object covered props, so you can use it to give some explanations, okay we accept
the implementation, so now you know there is a terminal, inline chat for file manipulation
and editor inline chat for manipulations with the code in the current file, and see you
in the next lesson.